<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TestProject</string>
    <string name="opening_text">This project written by Test tasks.
        Shows random information in list view.
        Please, press on button below for launch.
    </string>
     <string name="just_press">Please, press to read more about </string>

    <!-- array_of_titles  -->
    <string-array name="array_of_headers">
        <item>Valentina</item>
        <item>Ruslana</item>
        <item>Tamara</item>
        <item>Pauline</item>
        <item>Larisa</item>
        <item>Marina</item>
        <item>Diana</item>
        <item>Elena</item>
        <item>Bella</item>
        <item>Ann</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- array_of_descriptions  -->
    <string-array name="description_array">
        <item>Valentina light, like something in the spring sun temper.
            She can easily flare up, quarrel with her best friend,
            but not take more than two minutes, it is ready to go for reconciliation.
        </item>
        <item>Typically, this is an attractive and sensual woman.
            Ruslana chooses husband a long time. However, married, becomes a model hostess.
        </item>
        <item>Tamara almost always is the leader in the family.
            She is independent, is used to relying on their own strength.
        </item>
        <item>Pauline loves to dress up, has excellent taste, but economical,
            rather sew your attire itself, rather than spend on the shopping thing.
        </item>
        <item>Larisa does not impose their ideas and others experiences,
            although many take to heart as easily vulnerable.
        </item>
        <item>Marina high opinion of himself.
            A beautiful Marina often overestimates himself even.
        </item>
        <item>Name Diana sounds hard, and in the character of this girl
            really quite pragmatic, even hardness and obstinacy.
            Because of these qualities it is possible to achieve success in life.
        </item>
        <item>Elena will likely not marry a rich and beautiful, and she prefers a man who regret.
            Not sparing herself in her sacrificial love, Elena expects the same attitude.
        </item>
        <item>Bella principle and prudence, though often acts impulsively.
            Communicative and sociable, quickly making new acquaintances.
        </item>
        <item>Ann never forgets about her appearance - she knows how to dress nicely,
            just visit the hairdresser.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
